christyscozycorners.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Christy's Cozy Corners

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://christyscozycorners.com. This policy is effective from 5/18/2018.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

Christy’s Cozy Corners keeps contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, but we do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

MadMimi – this is the email service I use to send new content to my subscribers. If you subscribe, your email address will be kept until you unsubscribe.

Advertising – this service is third party advertising who may collect your data or IP address and have their own privacy policy in place. Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

Affiliate networks – this website participates in affiliate marketing. Certain links may lead you to sites where you can make a purchase. They will collect information based on their privacy policy. . You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

We may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of Christy’s Cozy Corners. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

## Your contact information

If you have questions regarding your contact information or other issues regarding our privacy policy, contact christy41970 (@) gmail.com

## Smush Plugin

Smush sends images to the WPMU DEV servers to optimize them for web use. This includes the transfer of EXIF data. The EXIF data will either be stripped or returned as it is. It is not stored on the WPMU DEV servers.

Smush uses a third-party email service (Drip) to send informational emails to the site administrator. The administrator’s email address is sent to Drip and a cookie is set by the service. Only administrator information is collected by Drip.

## Askimet

We collect information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect depends on how the User sets up Akismet for the Site, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

## Really Simple SSL

Really Simple SSL and Really Simple SSL add-ons do not process any personal identifiable information, so the GDPR does not apply to these plugins or usage of these plugins on your website. You can find our privacy policy [here](https://really-simple-ssl.com/privacy-statement/).

Bootstrapped Ventures, the developer of WP Recipe Maker, does not have access to any of the data collected by the plugin. This is all stored in your local database and not communicated back to us. Take note of the following topics for your own privacy policy.

## Source: WP Recipe Maker

Bootstrapped Ventures, the developer of WP Recipe Maker, does not have access to any of the data collected by the plugin.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When comment ratings are enabled we store the rating a user has given to a recipe along with the personal data WordPress core stores.

### Cookies

When user ratings are enabled we store a WPRM_User_Voted_%recipe% cookie (with %recipe% the ID of the recipe) that contains the rating this user has given to a particular recipe. This cookie is used as (one of the) measures to prevent rating spam.

### IP Address

When user ratings are enabled we store the IP address upon voting. This is used as (one of the) measures to prevent rating spam.

### Their own manually input information

With the Recipe Submission feature personal data can be collected, depending on the fields that were added to the form. This can include the user email and name. When using the reCAPTCHA feature you will be agreeing to their terms of use and privacy policy.

## How long we retain your data

Our cookies are stored for 30 days. User submitted data is stored indefinitely in the local database.
